QUINCY PHAM

Seattle, WA ↑
(206)226-1752 ↓
quincytpham@gmail.com ☑
linkedin.com/in/quincytpham iii

http://quincytpham.com/

Skills Summary

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, NodeJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, EJS, Python, Django, SQL, PostgreSQL, SASS, Bootstrap, Semantic UI, AJAX, REACT, AngularJS
- Teamwork, Leadership, Troubleshooting, Problem-solving, Technical Communication, Customer Service
- Git / GitHub, Agile / Scrum, Slack, Trello, Zoom, Microsoft Office, Adobe Creative Suite, WordPress / CMS

Project Highlight

General Assembly Capstone - Project Community:

 Project Community is a community resource application, utilizing Django and PostgreSQL, intended to aid COVID-19 relief and those in need of community resources. The design philosophy is to make things as simple and accessible as possible to transform as many lives as possible. Key tasks being planning, researching, and creating the resource database, and developing code that utilizes location data and text/language accessibility options to return relevant information for users to seek assistance in healthcare, food, shelter/housing, employment, education, utilities/finances, disability and other services.

Education

Computer Software Engineering Bootcamp | 2021

General Assembly

Microsoft Technology Associate Certifications | 2016

- Database Fundamentals
- Networking Fundamentals
- Windows Operating System Fundamentals

Bachelor of Art in Communication | 2015

University of Washington, Seattle

Associate of Art in Business | 2011

Seattle Central College

Work Experience

Child Support Enforcement Officer / Caseworker | MARCH 2018 - PRESENT

WA State Department of Social and Health Services

Site Lead / Coordinator | OCTOBER 2017 - MARCH 2018

Seattle Public Schools - Team Read

Lead Coding Instructor | SEPTEMBER 2016 - OCTOBER 2017

Creative Coding 4 Kids

System Administrator & Web Developer | OCTOBER 2013 - OCTOBER 2015

University of Washington, Seattle